

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

PHP NodeJS Python MySQL Elasticsearch

PERSONAL SKILLS

Googling Learn Coding Surf in Stackoverflow

CONTACT

P: +62 813 179 061 40 E: fahmiprasanda@gmail.com W: fahmiprasanda123.github.io

SOCIAL

fb.me/fahmi.einsten

instagram.com/fahmiprasanda

twitter.com/fahmiprasanda

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fahmi-prasanda-5a1b97ab/





FAHMI PRASANDA

PROGRAMMER

ABOUT

I am an experienced programmer in start up, software house, and agency. Now I'm continuing my studies at Pakuan university with non-regular classes majoring in computer science. I am always challenged by the world of programming and data

WORK EXPERIENCE

PROGRAMMER

Komiqus | April 2019 - Dec 2019

• Develop Social Commerce With PHP and Angular

PROGRAMMER

PT.Muhammad Abdul Azis Indonesia | Dec 2019 - April 2020

• Developed Accounting Web Application for NRA Group

PROGRAMMER

PT.Bintoro Sinergi Korpora | July 2020 - April 2021

- Develop Website Company Profile For Bussiness Units in Bintoro
- Develop Multisite Web Application for Constuctor and E-commerce (Binggo)

PROGRAMMER

PT.Daksa Adi Data (Artha Graha Group) | April 2021 - Present

• Develop Data Science System For Internal

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA OF INFORMATION SYSTEM PAKUAN UNIVERSITY | 2016 - 2019 GPA 3.61

BACHELOR DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE PAKUAN UNIVERSITY | 2019 - PRESENT

CERTIFICATE

- INTRODUCTION TO DATA SCIENCE WITH R DQLab | AGT 2021
- INTRODUCTION TO DATA SCIENCE WITH PYTHON DQLab | AGT 2021
- R FUNDAMENTAL FOR DATA SCIENCE DQLab | AGT 2021
- PYTHON FUNDAMENTAL FOR DATA SCIENCE DQLab | AGT 2021
- Fundamental SQL Using SELECT Statement DQLab | AGT 2021